<cryptocurrencies>
    <BTC>
        <title>Bitcoin</title>
        <description lang="en"> Bitcoin is a digital currency created in January 2009. 
        created by the mysterious
        developer Satoshi Nakamoto, whose true identity has yet to be verified. Bitcoin 
        offers the promise of lower transaction fees than traditional payment mechanisms 
        and is decentralized, unlike government-issued currencies.</description>
    </BTC>

    <BTG>
        <title>Bitcoin Gold</title>
        <description lang="en"> Bitcoin gold was a hard fork of the original open source 
        cryptocurrency which took place on October 24, 2017. While hard forks take place 
        for a number of reasons,bitcoin gold's stated purpose has been to "make bitcoin 
        decentralized again."
        </description>
    </BTG>

    <BCH>
        <title>Bitcoin Cash</title>
        <description lang="en"> Bitcoin cash is a cryptocurrency created in August 2017, from 
        a fork of Bitcoin. Bitcoin Cash increases the size of blocks, allowing more 
        transactions to be processed. is referred to as Bitcoin Cash because it uses the 
        original Bitcoin Cash client. 
        </description>
    </BCH>

    <LTC>
        <title>Litecoin</title>
        <description lang="en">Launched in the year 2011, Litecoin is an alternative 
        cryptocurrency based on the model of Bitcoin. Litecoin was created by an MIT graduate 
        and former Google engineer named Charlie Lee.Litecoin differs from 
        Bitcoins in aspects like faster block generation rate and use of scrypt as a proof of 
        work scheme. </description>
    </LTC>

    <DASH>
        <title>Dash</title>
        <description lang="en">Dash (formerly Darkcoin) is a blockchain-based peer-to-peer 
        cryptocurrency that was forked out of Bitcoin to offer faster and more private transactions 
        to users than Bitcoin could deliver. Dash is a blendword for Digital Cash and its currency 
        symbol in the markets is DASH.</description>
    </DASH>

    <DOGE>
        <title>Doge</title>
        <description lang="en">Dogecoin is a peer-to-peer open source cryptocurrency and falls under
         the category of altcoins. Launched in December 2013 with a Shibu Inus (Japanese dog) as its
          logo, Dogecoin looked casual in its approach but is gaining wide acceptance for online 
          transactions. Dogecoin is scrypt based (i.e. based on a password key) and 
          enables fast payments to anyone, anywhere across the globe.</description>
    </DOGE>

    <XRP>
        <title>Ripple</title>
        <description lang="en">Ripple is a technology that acts as both a cryptocurrency and a digital 
        payment network for financial transactions. It was first released in 2012 and was co-founded by 
        Chris Larsen and Jed McCaleb.</description>
    </XRP>

    <XLM>
        <title>Stellar Lumens</title>
        <description lang="en">The Stellar network is a blockchain-based distributed ledger network 
        that connects banks, payments systems and people to facilitate low-cost, cross-asset transfers 
        of value, including payments. Stellar has its native cryptocurrency called lumens, which is 
        denoted by the symbol XLM. All three terms—Stellar, lumens and XLM—are used interchangeably, 
        though stellar is blockchain network, lumen is the cryptocurrency and XLM is its trading symbol.
        </description>
    </XLM>

    <ZEC>
        <title>ZCash</title>
        <description lang="en">ZCash is a cryptocurrency with a decentralized blockchain that provides 
        anonymity for its users and their transactions. As a digital currency, ZCash is similar to 
        Bitcoin in a lot of ways including the open-source feature, but their major differences lie in 
        the level of privacy and fungibility that each provides.</description>
    </ZEC>
</cryptocurrencies>